{
    "subject": "resource/United_Arab_Emirates",
    "predicate": "ontology/capital",
    "object": "resource/Abu_Dhabi",
    "human_readable": "The capital of United Arab Emirates is Abu Dhabi.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9527129530906677,
            "question": "Is Dubai the capital of the United Arab Emirates?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9259544014930725,
            "question": "What is the capital of the United Arab Emirates?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8273459076881409,
            "question": "Which country has Abu Dhabi as its capital city?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7848556637763977,
            "question": "What is the official capital of the UAE?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7202562689781189,
            "question": "What is the name of the UAE's capital city?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6120046377182007,
            "question": "Name a major city in the United Arab Emirates."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5779470205307007,
            "question": "Where is Abu Dhabi located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4139450192451477,
            "question": "Which city serves as the governmental center for the UAE?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1541101336479187,
            "question": "Which city hosts the UAE's presidential palace?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1508300006389618,
            "question": "Where are the headquarters of many UAE government ministries located?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The capital of United Arab Emirates is Abu Dhabi.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8979_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Which city hosts the UAE's presidential palace?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8979_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Which city serves as the governmental center for the UAE?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8979_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where is Abu Dhabi located?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8979_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8979_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8979_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8979_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8979_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8979_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8979_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8979_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8979_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8979_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8979_63.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple that \"The capital of United Arab Emirates is Abu Dhabi.\" This is explicitly stated in multiple documents, including file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_8979/re-ranker-msmarco/11.txt and file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_8979/re-ranker-msmarco/42.txt."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state that \"The capital of the United Arab Emirates is Abu Dhabi,\" which directly supports the query."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}